The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on. You wanna..?
噢，你用乒乓球打敗麥克真的太帥了。 你想要……?
You know, I'd love to, but I'm a little tired.
呃，我是想，不過我有點累了
- I'll put a pillowcase over my head. - You're on.
- 我會用枕套把頭包住的。 - 那來吧！
- Hey. - What's up?
- 嗨！ - 有事嗎？
Well, Mike's taking a shower, which, by the way, there's no law against.
麥克在沖涼 順便說一下，我們還沒有做那個...
And then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want..
我想去吃點東西，所以如果你們也想……
- Finally. - Is that Ross?
那是羅斯嗎？
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
是啊，那面破牆什麼聲音都包不住。
- Sounds like he's with someone. - He could be alone.
- 好像有人和他一起。 - 應該沒有吧
This morning I heard him do pushups and then talk to his triceps.
今天早上我聽見他做俯臥撐 後來還跟他的三頭肌說話。
Wait a minute, I think Phoebe's right.
等等，我想菲比是對的。
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
我也聽見有人和他在一起。
- Dr. Geller! - God, you're amazing.
- 蓋勒博士！ - 天吶，太不可思議了……
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
我剛想讓你這樣稱呼我呢。
- Oh, my God, that's Charlie! - She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
- 噢，天吶，是查莉！ - 他背著喬伊和羅斯亂搞！
Oh, that tart! Floozy! Giant!
噢，那個尖酸刻薄的……大……蕩婦……
- I'm not sure about this. - Yeah, you're right.
- 我不應該這樣 - 對，你是對的。
This is none of our business.
這根本不關我們的事。
I'm not sure it's the best way to hear everything. Get me a glass!
不，我應該找個方法好好的偷聽。 給我個玻璃杯！
No, I'm not gonna do this, okay? I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
噢，我不會那麼做的。 我不會偷聽我朋友的。
I love Barbados.
噢……我愛巴貝多！
I can't believe I'm kissing you. I'm kissing Rachel!
噢……我不敢相信我在吻你。 我在吻瑞秋啊！
I know. I'm her.
我知道，我就是她！
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
瑞秋和喬伊！是瑞秋和喬伊！！！
- What? - Get over here!
- 什麼？ - 過來這邊！
Oh, my God! I love how thin these walls are!
噢，天吶，我喜歡這些薄牆！
Thank you.
謝謝。
The One After Joey And Rachel Kiss
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, before, you said that nothing could happen between us. What changed?
嘿，之前你說我們是不可能的 為什麼又改變主意了？
Well, I only said that because of Ross.
之前這樣說是因為羅斯...
- And then I saw him kissing Charlie. - What?
- 可後來我看見他在吻查莉…… - 什麼？
Ross and Charlie?
羅斯和查莉？
Wow! She's really making her way through the group, huh?
哇！ 她真的很想加入到我們中來呢，呃？
- Eh, who am I to talk? - Yeah.
- 啊，說這個幹嗎？ - 啊....
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
真不敢相信，瑞秋和喬伊？
How about the dinosaur twins in the other room?
那邊那對恐龍二人組怎麼辦啊？
- No one is manning that wall! - I'm on it!
- 那堵牆沒人負責啊！ - 有我呢！
- Anything? - I think I hear curtains closing.
- 聽到什麼了？ - 我想我聽見他們在拉窗簾……
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
我們聽到鞋被踢掉了
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
彈簧床，不會錯的！
- You realize that's your brother. - Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
- 你有想過那是你哥嗎？ - 你說出來才想到。找個人來換我啊！
Wow! Wait a minute.
等等！
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
羅斯和查莉，喬伊和瑞秋，
Phoebe and Mike. We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
菲比和麥克！我們是唯一沒有換過人的一對呢！
That's not true. I came with Monica, I'm leaving with Weird Al.
不是啊！我和莫妮卡一起來的 卻要和古怪阿爾一起走。
Okay, I've had it with the hair jokes.
好吧，我受夠了這種頭髮的笑話了。
- Tomorrow I'm going to the salon. - Okay, Buckwheat.
- 明天早上，我們走之前我會去髮廊的。 - 好的，蕎麥人！
You gotta hear this, it's great! It's like free porn.
你們該來聽聽這個，太棒了…… 簡直就像是免費的A片！
- Is everything okay? - It's just.. I don't think I can do this.
- 呃……怎麼啦？ - 對，只是……我想我不能這麼做……
Oh, is it because of what might be on the bed?
噢……是否因為躺在床罩上？
- I saw that report, with the infrared.. - No! No.
- 我也看過那些報道了，在紅外線下和... - 不，不！
No.
不。
Look, I need to talk to Joey. I mean, you guys just broke up.
呃，我要跟喬伊談談。 你們才剛剛分手。
Before anything more happens between us, I need to know he's okay with it.
我們之間再發生什麼之前 我要確定他不反對。
- I completely understand. - All right, I'm gonna go find him.
- 我，呃……我完全明白。 - 好吧，我想我要去找他了……
I just need a second before I can, you know..
我想……我需要點時間…讓我那個……
Grandma, Grandma, Grandma.
外婆…外婆…外婆…
- Okay, I'll see you later. - Okay!
- 好了，過會兒見。 - 好的……
That's the door. He's gone.
關門聲，他走了……
And she's turning on the TV..
而她……打開了電視……
and watching Miss Congeniality.
在看……《選美特工》。
Honey? If you know it through a wall, you know it too well.
親愛的，如果你連這都聽得到 那你知道的就太多了！
Hey, what are you guys doing?
嘿，你們幹什麼呢？
We're just.. We're sad to go, so we're just saying goodbye to the hotel.
噢，我們在…… 快要走了，我們很傷心 所以在跟這旅館告別。
I love you..
我愛你……
Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
天堂旅店 高爾夫勝地和水浴……
Yeah. We had a great time, thank you.
對，我們玩得很開心，謝謝！
Bye.
再見！
Okay. Hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
OK, 呃…… 嗨，你們看見喬伊在哪兒了嗎？
He's probably in his room with his current girlfriend, Charlie.
他應該現在在他房間裡 和他現任女友查莉在一起。
That's the situation as we know it.
這就是我們知道的情況……
If you see him, could you tell him I'm looking for him?
好吧，如果看到他，告訴他我在找他好嗎？
- You got it. - Thanks.
- 沒問題！ - 謝了！
Thank you.
謝謝你！
Other wall, people! Other wall!
另一邊牆，夥計！另一邊！
- Rach, you there? - Oh, my God, that's Ross!
- 瑞秋，你在嗎？ - 噢，天吶，是羅斯啊。
- What are we gonna do? - Okay, just be calm.
- 怎麼辦？ - 噢，保-保-保持鎮靜。保持鎮靜。
For all he knows, we're just hanging out.
我們只是隨便聊聊。
All right? So just be nonchalant.
好嗎？ 隨意一點。
- That's not nonchalant! - No idea what it means.
- 這不叫隨意！ - 我不知道那是什麼意思。
Okay, just hide.
哦……好吧，躲起來！
- Rach? - Coming! Try under the bed.
- 瑞秋? - 來了！試試床下行不行！
There's no room under the bed..
床底不夠高啊。
- Is everything okay? - Yeah.
- 出什麼事了？ - 沒……
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is? - Hi.
- 嘿。     - 嗨… - 你知道喬伊在那兒嗎？
I really don't.
我真的不知道……
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yeah. Sure.
- 我能和你談談嗎？ - 當然，可以……
I don't believe this. Have you guys been..?
我簡直不敢相信……你們一直……
This is the listening side of the wall.
噓噓……趴在牆上好好聽。
Then she told me that she and Joey had broken up..
然後她告訴我她和喬伊分手了
and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
某程度上是因為她對我有感覺。
Right. Yeah.
呃呃……對……沒錯……
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out since the day I met her.
你知道嗎，我碰到查莉 的那天就想約她出去。
Oh, I know, I know. That's been really hard for you.
噢，我明白……我知道這對你來說很難。
Anyway, one thing led to another, and..
不管怎麼樣，事情一件接一件，而且……
before you know it, we were kissing.
噢……還沒知道是怎麼回事，我們接吻了。
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
你覺得喬伊會多生氣？
That is hard to say, Ross. That is hard to say.
這很難說，羅斯。這很難說。
I gotta find him. He's gotta be here someplace.
我要去找他了。他一定就在什麼地方。
You would think.
就是啊！
Joey?
喬伊!
- Is he gone? - How are you doing this?
- 他走了嗎？ - 你怎麼做到的？
What? Hey!
怎麼……哇……嘿！
What are you..? What is this? Have you been listening this entire time?
你們怎麼……這是怎麼回事？ 你們一直聽著嗎？
Yeah!
對！
Now, what is this?
那，這又是怎麼回事？
What is this? Well, let's see. We kissed for 10 minutes..
啊，這是怎麼回事？ 好吧，這麼說吧 我們吻了十分鐘
and now we're talking to our friends about it, so I guess this is sixth grade.
然後現在和朋友說這件事 我想只有六年級學生才這樣！
No, no. Have you thought about how complicated this could get?
哦，不……你想過這會變得多複雜嗎？
- What about Ross? - Well, he's with Charlie now.
- 羅斯怎麼辦? - 可他現在跟查莉在一起。
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you before anything really happens with her.
對，可他想在正式開始之前先和你說一下。
And as his friend, I mean, don't you think he deserves the same from you?
作為朋友，你們不覺得你們也應該這麼做嗎？
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
你戳到我痛處了，蓋勒兄妹！
Look, we appreciate all the advice..
好吧，很感謝你們的意見
but this is between Joey and me. We can handle it.
但這是我和喬伊之間的事，我們能處理……
We'll go. Will you do one thing for us, the people that care about you?
好吧，我們要回去了，可你能幫我們做件事嗎？ 為這些在乎你們的朋友...
- Sure. - Enunciate.
- 當然…… - 去說清楚！
Get out!
出去！
Are they right?
你覺得怎樣？
Probably, yeah. I mean, maybe we should..
可能吧，是…… 我是說
hold off until we talk to Ross.
我們應該先和羅斯說清楚。
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait. We don't have to do anything tonight.
對……對，我們可以等 我們今天晚上什麼事都不做。
Yeah, I think that would be best.
對，我想這樣最好……
So, I'm gonna.. I'm gonna take off.
那麼，那麼我要……我要走了……
- Although.. - I like "although."
- 除非…… - 我喜歡「除非」！
I mean, you know..
我是說
Ross and I haven't dated in, like..
我和羅斯已經有將近……
six years.
6年沒約會了。
Six years?
6年？
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
哇……跟讀高中一樣久了……
Plus, you know, he is with Charlie now.
而且，他現在跟查莉在一起。
Absolutely.
就是啊！
- He's not thinking about you. - No.
- 他已經對你沒感覺了。 - 是啊。
I'm thinking about you.
我才對你有感覺...
Yeah.
對……
- Let's forget about Ross. - It's forgotten.
- 我們忘了羅斯吧…… - 已經忘了。
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
-怎麼了？ - 沒事……
Seriously, what is it?
說真的……怎麼了？
Nothing. It's really.. It's nothing. Come here. Come here.
沒事……真的…… 沒事……再來……再來……
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Sorry, I just..
對不起，我只是，呃……
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
看起我來無法忽略羅斯……
Well, maybe I can help.
好吧，讓我來幫你忙吧。
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
哦，你的唇真軟……再來一次……
Yeah, we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.
你說得對……我們真的要跟羅斯談談……
Hey. You guys ready to go?
嗨！你們準備好要走了？
Not quite. Monica's at the salon, and I'm finishing packing.
還沒。莫妮卡還在髮廊，而我還沒收拾好。
Dude, you're not taking your Bible?
夥計！你不打算帶上你的聖經嗎？
You're not supposed to take that.
你不應該拿這個走的。
Besides, it's a New Testament. What are you gonna do with it?
而且這是新約，你要它幹什麼？
Learn about Jesus.
瞭解耶穌……
- Hey! - So did you talk to Joey?
- 嗨！ - 你跟喬伊說過了？
No. I couldn't find him. I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
呃，沒……還沒。我找不到她。 我會在飛機上跟他說。
Okay. Sounds like a good idea, Dr. Geller.
對，聽起來不錯……蓋勒博士！
Stop it.
別這麼說！
Ph.D.
PHD
You're filthy.
你真淫蕩！
- Hey. Have you guys seen Monica? - Actually, I think she went to the salon.
- 嘿，你們見過莫妮卡了嗎？ - 呃，我想她去髮廊了。
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went to the salon, all right.
哦，對，噢，她剛去了髮廊……
Check it out!
看一下！
Whose day just got better?
誰會最喜歡這個啊？
Chandler!
錢德！
Hey!
嘿!... 啊啊啊!
- What do you think? - I think..
- 你覺得怎麼樣？ - 我想……
I think I can see your scalp.
我想我能看見你的頭皮。
Don't you just love it?
你不喜歡嗎？
Yeah. Yeah, you got shellfish in your head.
對……對……對……你把貝殼掛在頭上。
It's something. You go, girlfriend.
真是太……那個了……去吧，女生！
- You never said that in your life. - Not once.
- 你以前沒這麼說過是嗎？ - 不止一次。
I thought so.
我想也是。
- Phoebe? - I'm so glad you did that.
- 菲比？ - 很高興你這樣做了！
Oh, and listen to this.
聽聽這個……
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes and the ears.
你知道嗎？…這真是對視覺...和聽覺的享受。
Wow, it's kind of weird that I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
哦，噢。哇, 我和查莉分手後還要坐在她旁邊，太尷尬了。
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados doesn't care about your social life.
就是說，巴貝多航空真是不關心你的私生活。
Does someone mind switching and sitting with Charlie?
嘿，有人想替我跟查莉坐嗎？
Oh, I mean, I.. Dude, I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
我……嘿！夥計，我跟查莉整個會議都混在一起了。
- I understand. - No, I'll do it.
- 我瞭解…… - 不，我要的。
Wish I could switch. I really don't want to sit with Allen lverson over there.
我也想跟誰換換。  我真的不想跟阿倫.艾佛森（籃球明星）坐在那兒。
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿！ - 嘿！
Once we're in the air and the captain turns off the seat belt sign..
呃……知道嗎，當我們升空 機長關閉繫好保險帶的標誌後……
you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你就可以自由的在我的小屋裡遨遊了……
And you should be careful when checking your overhead bins.
你檢查行李箱的時候要小心
- Because items may shift during.. - Oh, you're not good at this.
- 很容易和別人的搞混的... - 啊……這個你不在行……
- Do you have to go home tonight? - No, I think I could come over.
- 今天晚上你非要回家嗎？ - 不，我想我可以來過夜的。
It's Saturday, right?
今天星期六，不是嗎？
What?
怎麼了？
- I can't do anything tonight. - Why not?
- 呃……今晚我不行。 - 為什麼？
I have a date.
我有約會。
- You have a date? With who? - Oh, it's my girlfriend.
- 你有個……你有個約會？跟誰？ - 噢，是……我女朋友。
- You have a girlfriend? - Yeah.
- 你有……你有女朋友？ - 對……呃
Well, when you and I broke up, I started seeing someone.
之前我們分手後，我開始約會其他人。
- Well, for how long? - Three months.
- 那...多久了？ - 3個月。
Three months?
3個月?
Okay.
好吧……
This is none of my business, but how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
這可能不關我的事, 只是 呃……你認為你還會跟她好多久？
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner. I promise.
今天晚上晚飯的時候，我會告訴她結束了。 我保證。
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
噢，好吧……好的。那你去吧。
When you get home, maybe there'll be a special delivery package waiting for you.
然後當你回到家 可能會有個特別的郵包在那兒等著你。
Maybe I'll sign for it, tear it open.
我可能會簽收。撕開它。
- Pull out the packing material.. - We'll have sex. Let's leave it there.
- 扯開包裝材料……. - 你知道嗎，我們會做愛。你不用再說了
It's our last glimpse of Barbados.
這是我們看巴貝多的最後一眼了！
And my last glimpse of anything.
也是我看世間萬物的最後一眼。
All right, I'm gonna go talk to Joey. I think this is the right time.
好吧，我要去和喬伊談談。 我想現在是時候了。
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
空姐說完「duty free」(免稅)以後他總是情緒很好。 [註：喬伊聽成doody free（隨便做）了]
Okay. Good luck.
好，祝你好運！
You know, if he's not okay with this then nothing more can happen between us.
你知道, 如果他不能接受那我們之間就什麼都不能發生
I know.
我知道。
Well, if that's the case, I just want you to know..
恩, 如果事情真的那樣了我想讓你知道...
that I think I could have fallen for you really, really hard.
我認為我可能已經愛你非常非常深了
On the other hand, if he is okay with us..
另一方面來說, 如果他能接受
then, you know, it's cas, whatever.
那就...你知道...算了, 管他呢
Ross is coming over. I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
羅斯要過來了。 我想現在會是個告訴他的好時候。
I guess so. I'm just.. I'm really nervous.
我想是的。只是……我好緊張啊。
Well, keep in mind that by the time you're done..
好吧，你這樣想著： 你說完以後
they'll probably be serving dinner.
他們就上餐了。
Still nervous?
還緊張嗎？
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
我要吃寬麵條。
- Hey, Rach? - Yeah?
- 嗨，瑞秋…… - 怎麼！
- Do you mind if I sit here for a sec? - Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
- 介意我在這兒坐一會嗎？ - 不介意，當然不！不！
Good luck.
祝你好運！
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
So I..
我，呃……
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
有點兒關於查莉的事要跟你說。
- Yeah? - Last night, after you guys broke up..
- 怎麼？ - 好吧，昨天晚上你們倆分手以後……
So sorry to hear about that, by the way.
當然我覺得很遺憾…… 呃
Well, Charlie and I were talking, and..
查莉和我傾訴，然後……
Well..
呃
You kissed.
你們接吻了。
Wh.. What?
哇……什麼？
What? What would give you that idea?
你怎麼會這樣想的啊？
- I saw you. - Yeah, we kissed.
- 我看見了。 - 對，我們是接吻了
But nothing else. Nothing else happened, okay?
不過…什麼都沒發生，知道嗎。
- Ross, Ross, Ross. It's okay. - What?
- 羅斯……沒關係的。 - 什麼？
It's okay. You know, look..
這沒關係。
I totally understand, all right? You guys..
我完全理解，好嗎？ 你們...
make way more sense than her and I ever did, you know? And..
你比我更適合她。你知道嗎？ 而且……
- I want you to be happy. - Are you serious?
- 我希望你們幸福。 - 真的？
Yeah.
當然……
- Now I have something.. - I am speechless.
- 我也有點事想說…… - 我真是無話可說了……
I mean, the fact that you would put my happiness first like that, I mean..
你居然把我的幸福放在第一位。 我是說...
You're an incredible friend, do you know that?
你真是個令人難以置信的好朋友 你知道嗎？
- Well, look, before you go.. - No, I mean it.
- 噢……呃……呃……在你…… - 不，我說真的。
I mean, you're so loyal, man. And selfless and generous.
你既忠誠，又無私，慷慨……
I am those things, yeah.
我是，當然是。
I've known Chandler longer, so I think of him as my best friend. But now..
你知道嗎？我認識錢德更久 我也一直把他作為我最好的朋友
I may have to rethink some stuff.
不過現在…… 我想應該重新考慮一下了……
Dude!
夥計！
Hey, if there is ever anything I can do for you..
嘿，有沒有事情我能幫忙的？
I can't think of anything.
暫時還沒有……
- Thanks. - Yeah.
- 謝謝！ - 沒什麼！
- So hi. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- So you talked to Joey? - Oh, yeah. We had a really good talk.
- 你，呃，你和喬伊談過了？ - 啊，對。我們聊得很開心。
- Oh, that's great. - Yeah.
- 噢！太棒了！ - 對！
- So everything's okay? - Oh, no, it's great.
- 噢，一切都好嗎？ - 噢，不，簡直太棒了。
- It's great. He's an amazing guy. - Oh, well, obviously, I think so too.
- 太棒了。他真是……他真是好得讓人吃驚。 - 啊……呃，顯然我也這麼想。
Well, I'm so excited about this.
對，我感到很興奮。
Really? Excited?
真的？興奮？
What, are you kidding? I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
你開玩笑嗎？我現在做夢 都在想著要去幹那事……
Excuse me.
讓開！
You didn't tell him, did you?
你沒說是嗎？
I couldn't. He was saying all these really nice things about me.
我沒法說。他把我說得天花亂墜。
I didn't want him to get mad and take them back. I'm gonna edge out Chandler!
我不想惹火他，收回他說的話。  我快要頂替錢德的位置了。
Fine. Forget it. When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
好吧，好吧！回紐約以後，我跟他說。
Thank you. Yeah, I appreciate that.
謝謝。真的，我跟感激。
- Hi, Mike's place. - Hey, it's Mike.
- 嗨，麥克家。 - 嘿，是麥克。
- That was fast. - Oh, no, she's not here yet.
- 噢，真快。 - 噢，呃……不，她還沒來。
You know, I'm just gonna take off and break up with her over the phone.
知道嗎，我想我應該走了 我可以在電話上跟她說分手。
You can't do that. Oh, come on, Mike, strap on a pair.
不，你不能走！快用東西捆住自己！
Why don't you tell her that we got back together. Women appreciate honesty.
你為什麼不直接告訴她我們又在一起了。 知道嗎，女人欣賞誠實。
We also appreciate gentle spanking once in a while, just FYl.
也喜歡輕柔的拍打。
One more thing. There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
還有一件事……  可能……在我的咖啡台上有張Precious的照片。
Her name's Precious?
她叫Precious（珍貴）?
Is she a pure breed, or did you pick her up at the pound?
她是純種的嗎？ 你在獸籠裡挑的她？
- I just want to give you a heads up. - Okay. And if she gets upset..
- 不管怎麼說，我只想讓你知道一下。 - 好吧，噢，如果她傷心的話
just scratch her tummy and give her a liver snap.
記得撓撓她的肚子，逗她高興
What do you know, another hot blonde.
你知道嗎 又一個金髮女郎。
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
嗨，我是Precious，你是誰？
- I'm Phoebe. - Phoebe?
- 我……我是菲比。 - 菲比？
Mike's ex-girlfriend, Phoebe? The love of his life? That Phoebe?
麥克的前女友菲比？ 他一生所愛的？那個菲比？
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
噢，我真想快讓同事們快點看看這個……嗷！
- You go back to work tomorrow night? - Yeah.
- 明天晚上你就要回去工作了是嗎？ - 對！
So if you want people to see them..
那麼如果你想讓他們看
you're not having them taken out, say, at the break of dawn?
也就是說你今晚不會把他們解下啦？
Well, if I had them taken out, then I wouldn't be able to do this.
呃，如果我解下來了，我就不能這麼做了。
You like that, right?
你喜歡的，是嗎？
- What are you singing? - It's "Bolero" from 10.
- 你唱什麼呢？ - 《十全十美》裡的波利樂舞曲。
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
那是《現代啟示錄》裡的《狂熱的瓦格納》。
Here's the thing. The cornrows were a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
事情是這樣的：這些貝殼是用來解決 你頭髮的捲曲問題的。
Now that we're home, you don't have that problem. If you think about it..
而現在我們回家了，我們不再受那個問題困擾了 所以如果你考慮一下……
I hate them.
我討厭他們！
- What? You said you liked them. - Did I? Let's refresh.
- 什麼？你說過你喜歡的。 - 我說過嗎？我們回想一下。
I believe what I said was that I could see your scalp.
我想我說的是「我可以看見你的頭皮」。
Well, fine. So you don't like them. Everybody else does.
好吧，那麼你不喜歡。可其他人都喜歡。
Again, let's journey back.
再想想，讓我們想回到那次旅遊……
As I recall, Rachel said she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
我記得瑞秋說的是 她以前從沒注意過你的頭骨的形狀。
And Joey? Well, Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
還有喬伊…… 喬伊當時看不出你有什麼不一樣。
You know what? I don't care. I like it, and I'm gonna keep it.
知道嗎？我不管。 我喜歡這樣，喜歡它，而且我要留著它。
You're just jealous because your hair can't do this.
你嫉妒是因為你的頭髮不能這麼做……嗷！
- Get yourself in the tooth? - And the eye.
- 敲在你的牙上了？ - 還有眼睛！
Hi! There she is! Hi, Emma. Oh, my God, I missed you.
嗨……她來了。嗨,艾□。 噢，天吶，我想死你了。
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much. Hi.
哦，艾□，我真是太想你了，嗨！
Did you have a good time with Grandma Greene? Huh?
嘿……你和姥姥過得開心嗎？呃？
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again to use as a rattle?
她喋喋不休的時候給你興奮劑了嗎？
That was one time, Ross, and they were only, like, five milligrams.
只有一次，羅斯，而且只有5毫克。
Hey, Emma, Daddy has some presents for you, okay? I want you to wait right here.
噢，嘿，艾□，爸爸有禮物帶給你。 知道嗎？ 我想讓你在這兒等一會兒
Come here, sweetie.
等等，寶貝兒。
Ross, actually, there's something that I really need to talk to you about.
呃……羅斯 事實上我有點兒事要跟你說。
Okay, shoot.
好的，說吧！
- Okay. All right, here's the deal. - Oh, no!
- 好吧，呃……好的，事情是這樣的。 - 哦不！
- What is it? - Oh, major shampoo explosion!
- 怎麼了？那是什麼？ - 噢，大瓶的洗髮液破了！
- Look, Ross, this really isn't easy. - Oh, it's all over everything!
- 呃，聽著羅斯，這很難開口。 - 啊！！還沾得到處都是。
Why? Why me?
為什麼？為什麼偏偏是我？
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
因為你拿了300瓶洗髮液？
I guess things were just going too well for me.
我猜這些東西對我來說太珍貴了.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
對不起，對不起。你剛才說什麼？
- Well, yeah. Look, it's about me and.. - Oh, not another one!
- 好吧，呃……好吧，聽著，是關於我和…… - 噢，不要，又一瓶！？
Oh, my God.. Oh, and this is moisturizer! It's even harder to clean!
噢，天……是摩絲。這個更難清理！
Why? Why do bad things happen to good people?
為什麼？為什麼壞事總是落到好人的頭上？
- Wow. Clearly this is not a good time. - You think?
- 哇！好吧，很顯然這不是個好時候。 - 嗯，你覺得呢？！
Okay. Bye.
好的，再見。
All right, so Mike's on his way over.
好了，麥克已經回來了。
You thought you were meeting here, he thought at the restaurant, so..
知道嗎，你以為你們在這兒見 他卻以為在餐館見面 所以……
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong. The point is, I'm gonna take off.
誰對誰錯不重要 重要的是…… 我要走了。
Wait. I'm not letting you leave until you tell me what's going on. I mean..
你告訴我到底發生了什麼之前 我不會讓你走的。
are you guys getting back together or something?
我是說，你們和好了還是怎麼了？
All right.
好吧……
Susie.. Can I call you Susie?
蘇茜，我能叫你蘇茜嗎？
My name is Precious.
我叫Precious。
I can't say that.
對，可我叫不出口。
Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
呃……Susie，我想跟你直說……
Mike and I are back together. And unfortunately..
麥克和我和好了…… 並且，呃……不幸的是
that effectively ends your relationship with him.
這樣就要終結你們的關係。
He's very sorry about that, and wishes you the best luck in all your endeavors.
並且他對此感到很抱歉，並祝你好運。
I just can't believe this. Why?
我無法相信……為什麼？
- Well, I don't.. - Why would he do this?
- 這個我也不知…… - 噢，他為什麼這麼做？
- What's wrong with me? - There's nothing wrong with you.
- 我做錯什麼了？ - 沒有，你什麼也沒做錯。
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
我是說，現在我到底該做什麼？
Damn it, woman! Pull yourself together!
可惡！你這女人，鎮定點，鎮定。
Have some pride, for the love of God!
保持你的尊嚴，看在上帝的份上！
Okay, not a fan of the tough love.
好吧，你好像不喜歡苦澀的愛情。
I just can't believe that Mike didn't give me any warning.
我真不明白，為什麼他不給我點暗示在先呢！
He didn't know. He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados and proposing to me.
他之前也不知道的 他本來沒計劃到巴貝多向我求婚的……
He proposed to you? This is the worst birthday ever!
他向你求婚了？ 我這個生日真是糟透了。
Look, Precious..
聽著，Precious……
Mike's not worth this. You're an attractive, intelligent woman..
你不值為麥克傷心。 你是個迷人的、聰明的女孩
and let's face it, Mike's kind of a wang.
你看 麥克簡直有點混蛋。
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
我是說 他向我求婚的時候甚至還跟你在一起……
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
他居然想在你生日的時候跟你分手？
I don't like to kiss and tell, but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
並且，我本來也不想說的 不過這個週末他對你不忠的太多了。
Oh, my God, you know, maybe you're right. Maybe I don't need him.
噢，天吶，可能你說對了。 可能我並不需要他。
I deserve to be treated with respect.
我應該受到尊重。
Screw you, Mike. You're a coward and a bastard, and I hope you rot in hell!
你這個混蛋，麥克。 你這個膽怯的雜種，我希望你爛死在地獄裡。
You're welcome.
不用謝我！
Honey? You've been in there for a long time. Is everything okay?
親愛的，你在裡面好久了……沒事吧？
Not really.
有一點事。
I have a problem.
我出事了。
Really? What happened?
是嗎？怎麼了？
Well, I was dancing around and singing "No Woman, No Cry"..
好吧，我唱著《No Woman, No Cry》跳舞...
and I got stuck.
然後就掛住了。
- You can't move at all? - Oh, I can move.
- 一點都動不了？ - 噢，不，我可以動……
If I untangle you, will you please get rid of the cornrows?
如果我解開你，你會解開這個稻穗頭？
I guess so.
我想會……
- Some of these look a little frayed. - Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
- 有些看起來纏在一起了。 - 對，我自己試著解開過。
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- So? Did you tell Ross? - Well, I tried..
- 呃……你跟羅斯說了嗎？ - 沒有，我想說
but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
但他的洗髮液出事故了。
- So I guess now it's your turn again. - No, no, no, no.
- 所以我想該輪到你去了。 - 不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不……
I think it's better if you tell him. You know, it's easier for a woman.
我想最好是你去告訴他，知道嗎  這對女人來說容易些。
That way, you know, if he gets mad, all you have to do is go:
你知道，如果他抓狂了 你就可以……
"I didn't mean it.
我不是有意的。
I'm so sorry."
我太抱歉了。
Yeah, because that's what we do.
對，我們的確會這麼做的
All right, all right, okay. How about this? How about this? Tomorrow..
好吧，好吧，這樣，呃……這樣，這樣怎麼樣？
Tomorrow we'll both go and we'll tell him together.
明天……明天我們一起去，一起告訴他。
Okay, that sounds fair.
好吧，聽起來公平些。
- That just means, once again, we can't.. - I know.
- 可這樣我們又不能…… - 我知道，我知道……
That's okay. I mean, we can control ourselves. We're not animals.
不過沒問題。 我們有自制力，我們不是動物啊。
- No! Of course, we can wait. - Yeah.
- 當然，當然我們可以等。 - 是啊。
All right, so I guess that means good night then.
那麼我想該說晚安了？
Yep. Good night.
好的！晚安！
Good night.
晚——安！
晚安！
- Seriously, good night. - Stop saying good night.
- 說真的，晚安！ - 別說晚安了。
I'm so sorry.
好的。真對不起啊...
Look what I found in the drawer.
看我在抽屜裡找到了什麼……
And you said I'd never wear this.
你還說我永遠不會戴它呢。
Now that I untangled you, how about you do a little something for me?
我把你解救下來，你還沒報答我呢？
- Sure. What did you have in mind? - I think you know.
-當然，你想讓我怎麼報答？ - 你應該知道的啊。
- Really? I don't.. I don't really feel like it. - This is what I want to do.
- 真的？但我有點不想啊。 - 我就是想要。
Okay.
好吧。
I just don't get why you like it so much.
我不知道你為什麼這麼喜歡它。
She's an FBI agent posing as a beauty contestant!
她是個FBI特工，還參加選美呢。